-=TLF字幕组=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
反恐24小时
第九季 第10集
前情提要
我读了这份关于引渡鲍尔
I looked into the protocol of handing
去俄国的草案
Bauer over to the Russians.
引渡需要总统的亲自批准
Rendition requires the president's direct approval.
翻译 JasonLee
要他签字
He needs to sign.
詹姆斯·海勒
美利坚合众国总统
翻译 筱宸葭
翻译 lady5bird
办公厅主任
马克·布德罗
还要多久我们才能接管杰克·鲍尔？
How soon can we expect to take custody of Jack Bauer?
校对 诸星龟龟
特效 筱宸葭
难道您对此事会牵涉到
Is there some reason you are uncomfortable
海勒总统有什么难言之隐？
involving President Heller?
统筹 筱宸葭
克罗伊，遥控装置在我手上
Chloe, I've got the override device.
我想你帮忙看看
I want you to take a look at it.
我不去了
I'm not coming.
玛戈已经死了，没我什么事了
Margot's dead and it's not my problem anymore.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢我什么？
For what?
再一次机会
Another chance.
我知道这与亚当有关
I know that this was about Adam.
她丈夫向中国出卖机密
Her own husband selling secrets to the Chinese.
而她不知道？
And she didn't know?
特工
凯特·摩根
你说过要阻止分析员恢复
You said you were going to stop your analyst from retrieving
亚当·摩根被删的分区文件的
the deleted partitions from Adam Morgan's files.
如果他看到了那些分区，就会知道
If he sees those partitions, he's going to know that
我卖给中国的情报来源于你
you're the source of intel I've been selling to China.
有人能派给我么？
Is there someone you can send me?
清理工？
A cleaner?
我只是个中间人
I'm just a middleman here.
你酬劳不菲
You've been well-paid.
尽快解决
Sort it out.
艾德里安·克罗斯
他们找到乔丹了，史蒂夫，他死了
They found Jordan, Steve. He's dead.
出什么事了？
What happened?
不清楚，但是他们说发现了两具尸体
I'm not sure, but they said that they found two bodies.
两具尸体？
"Two bodies"?
CIA分局局长
史蒂夫·纳瓦罗
如果是那个我派去杀他的杀手
If it's the operative I sent to kill him
那我就会暴露了
he can be traced back to me.
我需要钱，证件和安全的逃离路线
I need money, paperwork and safe transport.
我知道遥控装置正往你那里送去
I understand the override device is on its way to you.
把它带来给我
Bring it to me
我会满足你的所有要求
and I'll make sure you have everything you asked for.
科伯恩将军派了一个国防部技术人员来分析它
General Coburn was sending over a DoD tech  to analyze it.
我们分析的这个东西
What we're dealing with here
可以无限制访问任何防御系统
unlimited access to any defense system out there.
杰克·鲍尔
我要查出这人是谁
I want to find out who this guy is.
在数据库里查查这人的指纹
I'm gonna run his fingerprints through the database
看能否找到匹配的
see if I can find a match.
我们有发现了
We have a hit.
他与谁有联系？
Who was he associated with?
史蒂夫·纳瓦罗
Steve Navarro.
以下事件发生在
晚上20:00 至晚上21:00 之间
基弗·萨瑟兰
摩根
Morgan.
凯特，我是杰克，我需要你帮忙
Kate, it's Jack. I need your help.
伊冯娜
斯特拉霍夫
怎么了？
What's going on?
杀乔丹那人是纳瓦罗派去的
The operative that killed your agent was sent by Navarro.
你说什么？
What are you talking about?
纳瓦罗和那个杀手曾同属一个秘密单位
Navarro and the killer were in the same covert unit together.
泰特
多诺万
纳瓦罗是他的联系人
He was his handler.
纳瓦罗为什么要杀乔丹？
Why would Navarro want Jordan killed?
玛丽·莱恩·莱杰斯库
我还没来得及和他对质
Before I could confront him
威廉·德韦恩
他就带上遥控装置跑了
he took off with the override device.
格本加
阿金纳格贝
凯特，事情比我们想象的更加危险
Kate, this thing is more dangerous than we thought.
不仅仅是无人机
It's not restricted to drones.
它可以访问多个武器系统
It can access multiple weapon systems.
迈克尔
温科特
甚至是其他国家的
Even those from other countries.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我现在在追他
I'm in pursuit now.
你派一队人马
I need you to send a tac team unit.
利用卫星和闭路电视
Use satellite and closed-circuit television.
定位我的手机，联系我
Lock into my phone. Get back to me.
本杰明·布拉特
基姆·瑞弗
东西带了吗？
Do you have it?
带了
Yeah.
我快到芬斯伯里广场了
I'm almost at Finsbury Square.
在利物浦街车站碰面
Meet me at Liverpool Street Station.
我怎么认出你？
How will I recognize you?
客 串
科林·萨尔蒙
马志
别担心，我会找到你的
Don't worry. I'll find you.
只要我拿到东西，车就会去接你
Once it's in my hands of course the car will arrive for you.
罗斯·麦克科尔
斯坦利·汤森
一切已经安排妥当
All the arrangements have been made
会送你安全出国
to take you safely out of the country.
亚当·辛克莱
菲利普·温彻斯特
我把东西交出来后，怎么知道
And once I hand over the device, how will I know you're gonna
你会不会遵守约定？
keep your end of the bargain?
你可以不遵守约定
Well...you can not keep up your end of the bargain
剪 辑
乔丹·戈德曼
然后你下半辈子就只能在联邦监狱过了
and spend the rest of your life in a federal penitentiary if you like.
如果你没被判死刑的话
That is, if you can avoid the death penalty.
艺 术 指 导
乔纳森·李
自己看着办
It's your choice.
我五分钟内到
I'll be there in five minutes.
喂
Hello.
怎么了？
What's going on?
我要把装置拿回来
I'm taking the override back.
耶茨的装置？
Yates' device?
是我的装置
My device.
你说过是耶茨设计的
Y-You told me that Yates designed it.
他只是改造了下
Yates engineered certain aspects of it.
摄 影
杰弗里 C·麦咖特
装置是我设计的
But I designed it.
他从我这偷的
He stole it from me.
音 乐
肖恩·卡勒里
针对美国无人机系统做了修改
And modified it for the U.S. Drone system.
制作人
金相圭
以便卖给恐怖分子
Just so he could sell it to terrorists
中饱私囊
and line his own pockets.
联合执行制片人
托尼·巴士加仑普
他从未想过这装置有更大的价值
Never gave a damn about the fact that it could be worth far more.
你说什么？
What are you talking about?
监 制
布莱恩·格雷泽
比杀害成百上千的无辜平民更大的价值吗？
Far more than killing hundreds of innocent people?
过来
Come here.
监 制
基弗·萨瑟兰
我们是在拯救生命，克罗伊
We're going to save lives, Chloe.
数百万人的生命
Millions of them.
监 制
强·卡萨
怎么救？
How?
我们会入侵全球的军械库
We're gonna break into the world's arsenals
找出防火墙的漏洞
and exploit a vulnerability in the firewalls.
监 制
大卫·弗瑞
我们会与全球每一个国家
We're going to share that information
共享此信息
with every nation on Earth.
监 制
罗伯特·科克伦
假如一个国家的武器系统可以被对手控制
How effective could a country's weapon systems be
那它还有多少用处呢？
if its adversaries could take control of them?
作用不大？
Not very?
监 制
曼尼·科托
没错，一举让技术战争成为过去
Right. So, one stroke and technological warfare is obsolete.
监 制
伊万·卡茨
霍华德·高登
艾德里安，装置被锁在中情局
Adrian, the override is locked up at CIA.
制 作 人
伊恩·史密斯
你怎么把它弄出来？
How do you expect to get it out of there?
已经弄出来了
It's out already.
纳瓦罗很快就会送过来
Navarro will be here momentarily to deliver it.
他和我曾做过交易
He and I did some business together.
他向我提供机密文件
He provided me with classified files
编 剧
乔尔·苏尔诺
罗伯特·科克伦
我再转卖部分资料给中国的情报人员
some of which I then brokered to the Chinese intelligence.
电视剧编剧
亚当·达西尔瓦
运作需要资金，克罗伊
Operations cost, Chloe.
我们也需要
Even ours.
中国人乐意付钱
Chinese were willing to pay.
编 剧
罗伯特·科克伦
曼尼·科托
伊万·卡茨
他们认为是在利用我
They assumed they were exploiting me.
其实是我在利用他们
I was using them.
都是为了共同的目的
It's all part of the same fight.
更好的世界
Better world.
导 演
米兰·切洛夫
你希望莫里斯和普莱斯考特生活的世界
A world you would've wanted for Morris and Prescott.
相信我
Have some faith in me.
我们就快成功了
We're so close.
来吧
Come on.
你愿意吗？
You with me?
愿意
Yeah.
请说！
Go ahead!
我是伦敦分局的加文·伦纳德
Gavin Leonard, West London Station.
摩根特工让我联系你
Agent Morgan instructed me to call you.
有什么发现？
What have you got?
纳瓦罗屏蔽了我们与监控系统的连接
Agent Navarro blocked our access to CCTV cameras.
网络连接-恢复中
我不确定要多久才能恢复
I'm not sure how long it's gonna take me to get us back in.
好吧，你转接到卫星上
Okay, I want you to switch over to satellite.
确定我的位置
Get a fix on my location.
让战术小队马上过来！
Get the tac team over here now!
好的
Will do.
妈的
Damn it.
利物浦街车站
我到车站西侧了
I'm approaching the west side of the station.
前方左手边应该有一堵
Should be a blue construction wall
蓝色的施工围墙
just ahead of you on your left.
我看到了
I see it.
我到了，我到墙这里了
Okay, I'm there. I'm at the wall.
水泥搅拌车里有个信封
You'll find an envelope in the cement mixer.
看到了
I see it.
东西我拿到了
Okay, I've got it.
很好
Good.
从你背后的洞口把装置扔过来
Drop the device through the slot directly behind you.
施工围墙的洞口
Through the construction wall.
快扔过来
Drop it now.
扔过去了，车呢？
Okay, it's done. Where's my car?
喂？我要的车呢？
Hello? Where the hell is my car ?
快说啊，王八蛋！
Talk to me, you son of a bitch!
别动！
Don't you move!
扔下武器！
Drop the weapon!
趴在地上！
On the ground now!
双手交叉放在头上！
Interlock your fingers behind your head!
趴下！
Down!
东西在哪？
Where is it?
遥控装置在哪？
Where is the override device?
拷上
Cuff him.
在哪！
Come on!
妈的
Damn it.
让开！
Out of the way!
Out of the way! Move!
让开！
警察办案！快让开！
Police emergency! Out of the way! Move!
克罗伊！
Chloe!
我是杰克
Yeah, it's Jack.
我要你追踪一列
I need you to track a train
从利物浦街车站向西开去的地铁！
leaving Liverpool Street Station heading westbound now!
三分钟前，地铁环线上
Someone triggered the emergency brake
有人在到达下一站前拉了紧急刹车按钮
three minutes ago on the Circle Line before the next station.
有两人在隧道里下车了
Two people on the train got off in the tunnel.
那里没有闭路电视
Where there's no closed-circuit television.
有预谋的，他们逃走了，多谢
This was planned. They're gone. Thanks.
请说
Go ahead.
杰克，我是凯特，开的免提，瑞特特工也在
Jack, it's Kate. You've got me and Agent Ritter on speaker.
我们回中情局了
We're back at CIA.
你那边什么情况？
What's your status?
我们抓到了纳瓦罗
We got Navarro.
不过他已经把遥控装置给艾德里安·克罗斯了
But he handed off the override device to Adrian Cross before I could get to him.
这事跟艾德里安·克罗斯有什么关系？
What does Adrian Cross have to do with any of this?
还不清楚
I don't know yet.
我会让所有特工搜寻他的下落
I'll put out an all-agency search on him now.
可以试试
You can try.
不过他过去十年都逃脱了当局的追捕
But Adrian Cross has spent the last decade eluding authorities.
凯特
Kate.
克罗伊·奥布赖恩和他在一起
Chloe O'Brian was with him.
杰克，你确定？
Jack, are you sure?
确定，我看到她了
Positive. I saw her.
我打过电话，但是打不通
I tried calling, but the line's dead.
这说不通啊
That doesn't make any sense.
克罗伊一整天都在帮我们
Chloe's been helping us all day long.
如果不是她，我们根本没法及时抓住玛戈
If it wasn't for her, we wouldn't have gotten to Margot in time.
我知道
I know.
你认为奥布赖恩在耍我们？
You think O'Brian was playing us?
等我们拿回装置后
Biding her time until we got the device back
再把东西给克罗斯？
so she could give it to Cross?
我看不像，不过我也不确定
My gut says no, but I can't be sure.
我马上带纳瓦罗回去
I'm coming in with Navarro now.
好的
All right.
现在你级别最高
You're the ranking now.
请大家听我说
Can I have everyone's attention, please?
你们有人已经知道了
As some of you may already know
纳瓦罗局长因为涉嫌谋杀
Station Chief Navarro has been taken into custody
技术员乔丹·里德以及盗窃
as a suspect in the murder of analyst Jordan Reed.
今日恐怖袭击中使用的遥控装置被拘捕了
And for the theft of the override device used in today's attacks.
作为高级特工
As senior agent
由我暂时负责分局的事务
I'm assuming the duties of station head for the time being.
找回装置
Recovering this device
是我们的头等大事
is our number one priority.
我马上会给大家分配任务
I'll be issuing protocols and responsibilities shortly.
谢谢，大家回去工作吧
Thanks. Let's get back to work.
你登录乔丹的系统
I need you to get into Jordan's system
看看他负责的事情
and see if he was working on anything
是否和纳瓦罗有关
specifically to do with Navarro.
事情大到要杀了他？
What, something worth killing him for?
爸，服药期间不能喝酒
Dad, you-you can't mix alcohol with your medication
就一口
Just the one.
他们让我告诉你
I was asked to tell you
空军一号在机场准备好了
that Air Force One is on the tarmac. It's fueled and ready.
很好
Good.
我来这是为了保住迪戈加西亚岛的无人机基地
You know, I came over here to keep our drone bases in Diego Garcia.
现在却要空手而回
And now I'm going back with nothing.
除了那些无辜牺牲的英美平民让我良心不安
Except a slew of British and American lives on my conscience.
你不必为阿尔哈拉兹的所作所为担责
You are not responsible for what Al-Harazi did.
你甚至愿意为了救其他人放弃自己的生命
You were willing to give up your life to save others, Dad.
你无须自责
Do not blame yourself for anything.
这个问题留给历史学家评价吧
I think I'll leave that one up to the historians.
我们该通知特勤局
We should tell the Secret Service
我准备回国
that I'm ready to go home.
打电话给副总统
Put in a call to the vice president.
告知他我准备发表声明
Tell him that I'm getting ready to make the announcement
让他准备接任总统
and he should prepare himself to take over.
爸
Dad.
这个我们已经讨论过了
we've already talked about this.
他会在安德鲁斯机场…
Yeah, he's gonna be at Andrews...
阁下
Sir.
马克，拜托
Mark, please.
伦敦分局的瑞特特工来电
Agent Ritter is calling from the West London station.
他要立即和您通话
He needs to speak to you immediately.
电话接过来
Well, put him on.
过来
Come here.
瑞特特工，可以和总统通话了
Agent Ritter, you're on with the President.
总统阁下
Mr. President.
我来电是通知您今日恐怖袭击中
I'm calling to alert you that the override device
使用的遥控装置在我们分局被盗了
used in today's attacks was stolen from our facility.
我们相信装置在艾德里安·克罗斯和他的人手上
We believe that Adrian Cross and his people are in possession of it.
怎么会这样？
How did that happen?
瑞特特工
Agent Ritter
你们的分局局长纳瓦罗在哪里？
where is your station chief, Navarro?
纳瓦罗特工正是盗窃装置的人
Agent Navarro was responsible for the theft.
什么？
What?
杰克·鲍尔刚刚抓到了他
Jack Bauer just apprehended him.
总统先生，事关重大，您必须知道
Mr. President, it's important that you understand
这个装置远比我们预料的要危险得多
that this device seems to be far more dangerous than we realized.
为什么？
How's that?
国防部派来的技术人员
The tech that the DoD sent over
在完成分析之前
was assaulted by Navarro
被纳瓦罗攻击了
before he could complete his analysis.
但似乎从他的记录中可以看出
But it seems, from his notes
这个装置可以越过
that this device can get past
大部分国家用来保护军事指挥
the basic firewall security most countries use
和控制系统的基础防火墙
to protect their military command and control systems.
鲍尔现在在哪里？
Where's Bauer now?
他正在押解纳瓦罗
He's transporting Navarro
回来审问
back here for interrogation.
等他一回去，给予全面支持
When he gets back, give him everything he needs.
随时向我汇报
And keep me posted.
是，先生
Yes, sir.
我要国防部做一份完整报告
I want a full report from DoD
还有他们能想到的
and any countermeasures
任何对策
that they can think of.
是，先生
Yes, sir.
还有，马克，通知空军一号推迟行程
And, Mark, tell Air Force One to stand down.
不解决完这件事，我们哪里也不去
We're not going anywhere till we figure this out.
明白
Got it.
摩根特工
Agent Morgan
我想我找到了点线索
I think I found something.
和纳瓦罗有关？
That connects to Navarro?
是的
Yeah.
在乔丹离开之前
Before Jordan left, he was running
他正在恢复一些数据
some data restoration protocol.
他想恢复什么？
What was he trying to recover?
纳瓦罗去年负责的一些文件
Some files that Navarro was working on
而之后又被删除了
sometime last year, and then deleted.
那些文件…
Those files...
里面含有应该是你丈夫泄露给
they contained classified material that was supposedly leaked
中国的机密情报
to the Chinese by your husband.
这些情报都来源于纳瓦罗
The intel originated from Navarro.
你的意思是纳瓦罗才是
You're telling me Navarro was the one
向中国出卖情报的人
who sold the intel to the Chinese
但是他设计成好像是我丈夫干的
but he made it look like my husband did it.
他陷害了我丈夫
He set my husband up.
是这样吗？
Is that right?
是的
Yeah.
那个狗娘养的！
That son of a bitch!
凯特！凯特，先等等
Kate! Kate, hold on.
不，你明白他干了什么吗？
No, do you understand what he did?
我明白，我清楚
I-I get it, I get it, I know.
但是现在不是时候，也不该在这里
But this is not the time or place.
先回你办公室
Go to your office.
我办不到
I can't do that.
回去，马上
Go. Now.
这是命令
That's an order.
这是怎么了？
What's that about?
我还在调查纳瓦罗还干了什么
I'm still finding out what else Navarro was into.
看样子就是他把机密情报卖给了中国人
Looks like he was the one who sold secrets to the Chinese
又陷害了凯特的丈夫，让他做替罪羊
and set Kate's husband up to take the fall.
我正在取得授权
I'm getting authorization
把他移交给特勤组
to have him sent down to special activities
严加审问
for enhanced interrogation.
那没用的
That's not gonna work.
纳瓦罗在谍报中心干过
Navarro was in covert ops.
接受过所有反审讯训练
He's been trained to resist those exact same techniques.
你有何高见？
What do you suggest?
让我来跟他谈
Let me talk to him.
鲍尔
Bauer.
他把你
He views you
和其他人都看成下属
and everybody else here as a subordinate.
他根本不会怕你
He will not be afraid of you.
但他清楚我的过去
But he knows my history.
好吧
Okay.
好吧，他一被押到审讯室
Okay, you can talk to him
你就可以和他谈
as soon as he's set up in interrogation.
但要是你做得过分了，我会把你拽出来
But if you cross the line, I'm pulling you.
话得说清楚
Just so we're clear.
我不是在请求
I wasn't asking.
只是先礼后兵罢了
That was me being courteous.
凯特
Kate.
我不需要你说什么
I don't need you to say anything.
我知道
I know.
至少你的丈夫沉冤得雪了
At least your husband's name has been cleared.
不
No.
太晚了，杰克
It's too late for that, Jack.
我丈夫被判终身监禁
My husband got a life sentence
服刑一个月，他上吊自杀了
and a month into it, he hung himself
都是因为那个狗娘养的
all because of that son of a bitch
我还把他当成朋友
who I thought was my friend.
我很难过
I'm sorry.
我得去审问纳瓦罗了
I have to interrogate Navarro.
我们得找到遥控装置
We need to find the override device.
要不要参与，你自己决定
You need to decide whether or not you want to stay in.
如果你选择回避
Nobody would fault you
没人会怪你
if you chose to step aside
尤其是我
especially me.
好的，数据出来了
Okay, the readings are coming in.
不出你所料，呼吸和体温都上升了
Respiration and thermal elevated, as you'd expect.
我们很难得到有效数据
Gonna be hard to get a reading
除非把他降到基准线
until we get him settled into a baseline.
我不需要生物统计数据
I don't need biometrics.
只要你记住底线
As long as you remember the ground rules.
好吧
Right.
我想在一旁观察
I'd like to observe.
我没事
I'm fine.
松开手铐，房间里就我们俩
Take off the restraints. Give us the room.
你清楚审讯程序，但我还是
You know the drill, but I'm gonna
要跟你过一遍
lay it out for you anyways.
中情局获悉
The CIA knows
你派人谋杀了里德特工
you had Agent Reed murdered.
又一直把机密情报卖给中国人
That you've been selling secrets to the Chinese
而且嫁祸给了摩根特工的丈夫
and had Agent Morgan's husband framed for it
他也是联邦特工
who was also a federal agent.
我亲眼看见你偷窃了遥控装置
I am an eyewitness to you stealing the override device
交给了艾德里安·克罗斯
and handing it over to Adrian Cross
你知道该装置是一种
knowing its full potential
大规模杀伤性武器
as a weapon of mass destruction.
你只有一种结局
There is only one outcome here
那就是死刑
and that is the death penalty.
当然了，除非
Unless, of course
你能合作
you cooperate.
帮我们找到它
Help us find it.
之后我才能保证
Then I'm pretty sure I can get them
你能免除死刑
to take that off the table.
实际上，我从不知道自己是和艾德里安·克罗斯做交易
The truth is, I never knew I was dealing with Adrian Cross.
他一直匿名地联系我
He kept all of our interactions anonymous.
但我知道你怎样能找到他和遥控装置，如果你动作够快的话
But I do know how you can find him and the override, if you move quickly.
作为条件，我要完全豁免权
In return, I want full immunity.
由总统签署，就这样，没得商量
Signed by the president. Period. No negotiations.
谈话到此为止
End of discussion.
没人会给他豁免权，对吗？
Nobody here is gonna give him immunity, right?
在你想要拒绝前
And before you bother to object
记住，我们在谈的可是大规模杀伤性武器
remember, we are talking about a weapon of mass destruction.
是不是，杰克？
Aren't we, Jack?
我好声好气地最后问你一遍
I'm gonna ask you one last time nicely.
遥控装置在哪里？
Where is the override device?
省省吧，你我都知道
Come on now. You and I both know
他们不会让你把我怎么样的
they're not going to let you hurt me.
瑞特特工是这里的总负责了
Agent Ritter is acting Head of Station.
他才不会让你毁了他的前程
There's no way he's gonna let you screw up his career.
识时务吧，杰克
Let's face it, Jack.
我早晚会得到豁免权
Anything you say or do between now and me getting that immunity
你这纯粹是在浪费时间
is just a waste of time.
滴答…时间不等人
Ticktock.
我可以跟你保证
Well, I can assure you
你想要完全豁免权，这绝对不可能
full immunity is not on the table.
倒是你的手就难说了
But your hand is.
东西在哪里？
Where is it?
遥控装置在哪里？
Where is the override device?
该死的，鲍尔！
Damn it, Bauer!
把他撵出去！医生！医生！
Get him out of here! Medic! Medic!
放开我！
Get off of me!
医生！
Medic!
叫个医生过来！
Get a medic in here!
凯特，别这样！
Kate, don't!
你不会逍遥法外的！
You're not gonna get away with this!
亚当的命得算在你头上！
Not after what you did to Adam!
出去！叫一个警卫看住他！
Go! Put a guard on him!
带他到医务室
Take him down to medical.
不许任何人靠近他！
No one near him!
你不能和这种人做交易
You cannot make a deal with this man.
出去！听我说，凯特
Go! Listen to me, Kate.
听我说
Listen to me.
如果纳瓦罗真的知道怎么找到遥控装置
If Navarro really knows how to find the override device
那么我就不得不
then I have to make the case
争取豁免权，用来交换
for immunity in return for information that might
能找到装置的信息
lead to the recovery of the device.
其余的由总统来定夺！
The rest is up to the president!
总统要起草一份对史蒂夫·纳瓦罗的
The president wants an immunity agreement
豁免同意书
drawn up for Steven Navarro.
凭他这样所作所为？真难以理解
That's hard to understand after what he did.
你没必要去理解，只要起草出来给我就行
You don't have to understand it, just draft it up for me
越快越好
as soon as possible.
好的
Okay.
司法部长也要签名
The AG needs to sign off on it, too
所以联系一下司法部门
so, set up a link to the Justice Department.
你想让我用办公室电话还是私线联系？
Do you want me to patch it through to the office or the cell?
长官？
Sir?
恩，用办公室的吧
Oh, uh, the office.
谢谢，罗恩
Thanks, Ron.
没问题
You got it.
很抱歉在我父亲面前
I'm s...I'm sorry that I snapped at you
冲你大声嚷嚷了
when I was with my father.
没事的
Okay.
马克，听着，我知道他
Mark, look, I know that he put you
让你左右为难，命令你绝对不能告诉我
in an impossible situation, ordering you not to tell me
他把自己的命交给了阿尔哈拉兹
that he was turning himself over to Al-Harazi.
但事实并非关于这件事的，对吗？
But that's not what this is really about, is it?
是我俩的隔阂？
The distance between us?
你什么意思？
What do you mean?
杰克·鲍尔在伦敦一出现
The moment Jack Bauer showed up in London
你就变了
things changed for you.
事实如此
That's the truth.
承认吧
Admit it.
马克
Mark.
杰克和我之间的事
what happened between Jack and I
已经结束很久了
that was a long time ago.
或许是的，不过很明显
That may be true, but clearly
你对他还余情未尽
you have not resolved your feelings for him.
你为什么提这个？
Why are you going there?
因为我厌倦兜圈子了
Because I'm tired of dancing around like this.
我只想知道我们走到哪一步了
I-I want to know where we stand.
我对我们的婚姻做出了承诺
I made a commitment to our marriage.
而且会恪守承诺
And I intend to honor it.
哦，那我很高兴，你是对我
Well, I'm glad that I'm an obligation
认真负责的
that you're taking seriously.
我不是这个意思
That's not what I meant.
那你什么意思？
What did you mean?
你这幅样子，我没法和你沟通
I can't talk to you when you're like this.
奥德莉
Audrey.
我是马克·布德罗
It's Mark Boudreau.
让他接电话
Put him on the phone.
我希望你打来是要告诉我
I hope you're calling to tell me you have
你抓到了杰克·鲍尔，想把他移交给我们
Jack Bauer with you to turn over to us.
还没有
Not exactly.
莫斯科方面听到这个会大失所望的
Moscow will be very sorry to hear that.
他们会让美国国务院知晓
They'll be letting your State Department know
你伪造了总统的签名
you forged your president's signature
使鲍尔的引渡令生效
on Bauer's rendition order.
我猜你可能要在监狱里了却余生了，我的朋友
I suspect prison may be in your future, my friend.
听着，鲍尔没在我手上
Look, I... I don't have Bauer
但是我能告诉你如何找到他
but... I can tell you how to find him.
接着说
Go on.
他在外行动
He's in the field.
他所用的是中情局的加密通信路径
He's using an encrypted CIA comm link.
我有传输代码
I have the transmission code.
你的人可以锁定他的位置
Your men will be able to pinpoint his location.
这才像话
That would be satisfactory.
我的助手会在一个安全频道发短信你
My aide will text you on a secure channel.
上传密码到他那里
Upload the code to him there.
不用多说了
Needless to say
这件事只有你我知道
my involvement in this remains between us.
如果我们成功抓住了鲍尔
If we successfully acquire Bauer
没人会知道此事
no one will ever need to know.
艾德里安？拿到手了吗？
Adrian? Do you have it?
是的，都准备好了吗？
Yes. Is everything ready?
哦，是的，我们将在15到20分钟内
Oh, yeah, we should be fully operational in about
全面运行吧？
15 to 20 minutes?
行，克罗伊和我到时候见你
Right. Chloe and I should see you then.
你全都告诉她了吗？
Have you told her everything?
是的，一会儿再聊
Yes. Speak to you shortly.
好的
All right.
艾德里安？
Adrian?
嗯
Yes.
我想去小便，不好意思
I got to go pee. Sorry.
好吧，快点
Well, hurry up.
嗨！
Hey!
克罗伊？
Chloe?
等一下，等一下
Wait. Wait.
不，等等！等等！
No. Wait! Wait!
别走！
Don't go!
把那给我
Give me that.
快把那个给我！
Just give me that!
快…把那个给我！
Just...give me that.
你为什么总是要让我失望？
Why do you insist on disappointing me?
你哪根筋搭错了？
What is wrong with you?
你好好想想，这不会成功的！
You can't actually think this would work!
我原以为在所有人当中
I would have thought, of all people
只有你最懂我
you might have understood it.
把武器分发给所有人吗？
Distributing weapons to everyone?
上车
Get in the car.
快上车
Just get in the car.
你是在问我还是在命令我？
Are you asking me or telling me?
我想你知道答案
I think you know the answer to that.
能给我点什么止痛吗？
How about giving me something for the pain?
上级命令我不能给你
I've been instructed not to.
不出所料
Naturally.
你给我举起手来
You get your hands up right now.
凯特，你在干什么？
Kate, what are you doing?
闭嘴，举起手来
You shut up. Get your hands up.
马上给我转过去
Turn around right now. Turn around.
靠墙跪下，你也是
Get against the wall now. On your knees. You, too.
跪下
On your knees.
凯特，你不必这样
Kate, you don't have to do this.
住口！你陷害了我丈夫
Stop it! You framed my husband.
他是因你而死
He is dead because of you.
想想你现在做的
Just think about what you're doing.
你还有大好的前程
You've got a long career ahead of you.
亚当被捕时，我自责没发现
Do you understand that when Adam was arrested, I blamed myself
他是间谍
for not knowing he was a spy
一直以来，你在我身边
and all the while, you stood by me
装作我的朋友
pretending to be my friend.
凯特，如果你杀了我
Kate, if you kill me
中情局永远都得不到装置
the CIA will never get their hands on that device.
我他妈才不管
I don't give a damn about that.
哦，冷静，冷静，凯特
Oh, oh, easy, easy, Kate.
鲍尔，让她放开我！
Bauer, get her off me!
凯特，放下武器！
Kate, put the weapon down!
滚开，鲍尔，这跟你没关系
Back off, Bauer. This has got nothing to do with you.
我们要留活口套得情报
We need him alive to know what he knows.
他什么都不知道，他在玩我们
He doesn't know anything. He's playing us.
不是这样，鲍尔！
That's not true. Bauer!
摩根特工，放下武器！
Agent Morgan, put it down!
他根本不知道装置在哪！
He's got no idea where the device is!
他根本没讲过实话！
He's lying just like he lied about everything else!
我没说谎，我在装置里放了追踪器
No, I'm not. I put a tracker on the device.
我知道它在哪
I can tell you where it is.
鬼话连篇的王八蛋！
You're a lying bastard!
凯特，放下武器让他说！
Kate, put the weapon down and let him talk!
我能告诉你追踪器密码
I can give you the tracker's code.
我不相信
I don't believe you.
我要一枪崩了你脑门
I'm gonna put a bullet in your head.
凯特！凯特放下武器！
Kate! Kate put the weapon down!
3-A-4-6-9-R
Three-A-four-six-nine-Romeo.
3A469R
Three, Alpha, four, six, nine, Romeo.
这是密码！我没说谎！
That's the code! I'm telling you the truth!
记下了么？
Did you get that?
加文？
Gavin?
开始启动追踪
Running the trace now.
似乎能用
Seems to be legit.
已开始四英里内的三角测量
It's already triangulating within a four-mile area.
收到，他在锁定遥控装置
Copy that. He's locking onto the override device.
奏效了
It worked.
你没价值了
You're done.
你会以谋杀和叛国罪
You're going to be executed
处以死刑
for murder and for treason.
我会去看你的
And I'm going to be there to watch.
到底发生什么了？
What the hell's going on?
摩根特工从纳瓦罗那挖出了情报
Agent Morgan broke Navarro.
我们锁定了遥控装置
We've got a lock on the override device.
得马上行动
We need to move immediately.
不知道艾德里安·克罗斯还会老实多久
We don't know how long Adrian Cross is gonna stay put.
凯特？
Kate?
中东武器系统
Weapon systems in the Middle East
也易被遥控装置控制
may also be vulnerable to the override.
中国航母进驻地中海
The Chinese carrier making its way into the Mediterranean
已让很多人神经紧绷了
is fraying a lot of nerves.
你有什么建议？
Well, what's your recommendation?
要告知北约么？
Should we alert NATO?
阁下，我对告知存有能侵入
Sir, I'd be very wary about broadcasting the existence
我们防御体系的装置持慎重态度
of a device that can access our defense systems.
不利于社会稳定
It would be extremely destabilizing.
抱歉来晚了，这是你要的豁免同意书
Sorry I'm late. Here's that immunity agreement you asked for.
没必要了
It's not gonna be necessary.
他们让纳瓦罗开了口
They managed to get Navarro to talk.
这是好消息
That's good news.
他说什么了？
What-what did he tell them?
他在遥控装置里安了追踪器
He installed a tracker on the override device.
但一切还是未知
We're not taking anything for granted.
只希望杰克和战术队能定位装置
We're just praying that Jack and the tac teams can locate it
尽快定位
and locate it quickly.
鲍尔参与了行动？
Bauer's involved in the operation?
是的，他带的队
Yeah, he's leading it.
好了，将军，我们要采取什么防护措施？
All right, General, what are we doing to protect ourselves against this?
所有军事部门都在全面戒备中
All branches of the military are on system-wide security alert.
加文，我们离进入搜寻边界
Gavin, we're approximately five miles
大概还有五英里
from the outer perimeter of the search grid.
锁定装置了么？
Do you have a location?
还要一会
It's taking a while to lock in.
有东西阻碍了信号
Something must be blocking the signal.
有办法解决么？
Can you do something about it?
我会试着传你大概坐标
I'll try and compensate, send you approximate coordinates.
搜索半径还是会很大
It's still gonna be a large search radius.
快点，战术一队
Work fast. Tactical One
收到没？
do you copy?
战术一队，收到
Tactical One, over.
我们不能同时进入
We can't enter as a convoy.
艾德里安·克罗斯的人一里开外就能认出我们
Adrian Cross' people will see us coming from a mile away.
你们从南边进入搜索
I want you to enter the grid from the south.
二队三队分东西两边进入
Teams two and three from the east and west, respectively.
收到
Copy that.
你还好么？
You okay?
最后一次见我丈夫时他正被拘禁
The last time I saw my husband, he was in custody.
我们正准备重新上诉
We were gonna go over his appeal.
他见到我非常高兴，直到发现
He was really happy to see me until he realized that
我不再信任他了
I no longer believed him.
我永远记得他的眼神
I'll never forget the look in his eye.
我知道就是在那时，他决定了结自己
I know that was the moment that he decided to take his own life.
不是因为被定罪，而是…
Not because he was convicted, but...
因为我抛弃了他
because I had deserted him.
这要我如何接受？
How am I supposed to live with that?
就这么接受
You just do.
四年前，我的搭档被杀
Four years ago, my partner
也是我的朋友
my friend was killed
我想尽一切办法复仇
and I took as much revenge as any man could possibly take.
我付出了所有，抛弃了家庭
It cost me everything I had, what was left of my family.
所有一切
Everything.
总以为这就能抹平伤痛，但没有
Somehow I thought it would ease the pain, but it doesn't.
不管怎样，你必须接受这点
And somewhere in your heart, you have to really accept that.
再开始原谅自己
Then you can begin to forgive yourself.
我把所有人都转移过来了
I've moved everybody over here.
这边走
Come on. This way.
这里原来是大学科研所，预算不够
Used to be a college tech lab. Budget cuts.
他们会很高兴看见你
They're all gonna be very happy to see you.
他们知道你关于装置的计划么？
Do they know what you're planning on doing with the device?
知道的
Yes, yes.
斯托什
Stosh.
克罗伊
Chloe.
克罗伊，克罗伊，我们得走了
Chloe. Chloe, we've got to go.
斯托什
Stosh.
克罗伊，克罗伊，快点
Chloe. Chloe, come on.
我们得走了
We've got to go.
快点
Come on.
别动
Stay right there.
程
Cheng.
把装置拿着
Take the device.
为什么要这么做？
Why did you do this?
什么，这个？
What, this?
我没有啊，是你做的
I didn't do this. You did.
是你想骗我们
When you tried to deceive us.
我们给你钱开发装置
We paid you to develop the override
不是让你公之于众的
not for you to give it away for the rest of the world.
你的政府本会
Your government would've got
拿到所买之物
what it paid for.
他不为中国政府效命
He doesn't work for the Chinese government.
奥布赖恩小姐
Ms. O'Brian.
这不是你的地盘
You are a long way from home.
你跟程合作？疯了么？
You're working with Cheng? Are you insane?
你是怎么认识他的？
How do you know him?
他效命中国情报局
He was with Chinese Intelligence
是洛杉矶中国领事馆的安保头目
headed security at the Chinese Consulate in Los Angeles.
被自己国家通缉
His own country had him arrested.
他本该把牢底坐穿
He's supposed to be rotting in prison.
他绑架了杰克
He kidnapped Jack
把他关在
had him put in a secret prison
北京郊外的密牢里，拷问了一整年
outside of Beijing and tortured him for over a year.
奥德莉·海勒去找他
When Audrey Heller went to go look for him
也被关了起来
he did the same thing to her.
装置被改过
The device has been altered.
你做了什么？
What have you done?
耶茨修改过
Yates modified it
侧重针对美国无人机，就是这样
so that it focuses on the U.S. Drones. That's all.
把它恢复初始状态
Well, you will restore it to the original state.
听着，我没本事做那种事
Look, I don't have the expertise for that sort of thing,
好么？
all right?
我相信你
I believe you.
但你一定能
But I'm sure you can manage.
对吧？
Right?
我不会帮你的
I'm not gonna help you.
不！
No!
下一枪就是他的脑袋
The next one is in his brain.
行，行，住手
Okay, okay. Stop.
我帮你
I'll help you.
快接电话
Come on. Answer the phone.
我是阿纳托尔·斯托纳维奇
This is Anatol Stolnavich.
请留言
Leave me a message.
阿纳托尔，这是我第三通留言了
Anatol, this is my third message.
撤掉你的人
Call off your men.
不要逮捕鲍尔
Do not apprehend Bauer.
收到后立即回电
Call me as soon as you get this.
加文，我是鲍尔，定位到装置没？
Gavin, this is Bauer. Do you have a lock on that location yet?
好了，两层建筑，四个地面入口
Affirmative. Two-story building, four ground entrances.
我在传送卫星信息，几个T-1干线
I'm showing satellite uplink, several T-1 trunk lines.
延时小于三分钟
You're less than three minutes out.
收到，地址发给摩根特工
Copy that. Send the address over to Agent Morgan.
记得叫后援，别拖太久
Don't wait too long for calling in backup.
我知道你和克罗伊·奥布赖恩打过交道
I know you have a history with Chloe O'Brian.
我首要任务是拿到遥控装置
My priority is the override device.
专心工作，不用担心我
Stay focused on your job. Stop worrying about me.
还要多久？
How much longer?
我不知道
I don't know.
你要是对这设备做什么手脚
If you're stalling or trying to do anything to compromise this device
我在进行缓冲区配置
I'm working on the buffer configurations.
要是那么容易，你也不会让我来干
If it was easy, you wouldn't have me doing it.
完成了会跟你说的
It'll be done when it's done.
你打算干什么？
What are you planning on doing anyway?
别管那么多
Don't concern yourself with that.
专心眼前工作就好
Just focus on the task at hand.
起来
Get up.
行了
We're good.
这里我能接手
I can handle it from here.
她植入的病毒呢？
What about the virus she planted?
正在删除
Deleting it now.
你的屏幕被他监视着
Your screen was mirrored by his.
就知道你会做手脚
I knew you were gonna sabotage the device.
你需要我接入固件接口
You needed me to access the firmware interface.
谢谢打开了门，奥布赖恩小姐
Thank you for opening the door, Ms. O'Brian.
我们不会活着出去的
We're not going to get out of this alive.
别这么说
Don't say that.
有些事…我要告诉你
There's something I...should tell you about.
你的丈夫和孩子
Your husband and your son.
什么？
What?
大约一年前
About a... year ago
我无意发现了些文档
I came across some documents that
推翻了你一直认为
disproved what you'd been led to believe about
他们死于车祸的
that car accident, their
想法
their deaths.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
那是场意外，克罗伊
It was an accident, Chloe.
没人企图杀你
No one was trying to kill you.
你家人发生的一切没有谁的责任
No one was responsible for what happened to your family.
为什么要瞒着我？
Why would you keep that from me?
我不想你走
I didn't want you to leave.
不管怎样，最终我还是要告诉你的
I was going to tell you eventually, no matter what.
真相永远是最好的
The truth is always the best.
什么真相？
What truth?
你决定好才说的真相么？
The truth when you decide to tell it?
看看周围，艾德里安
Look around, Adrian.
你所有的心血造就了这一切
All your work has led to this.
别指望我会后悔所站的立场
Please don't ask me to regret what I've stood for.
我不会的
I don't.
我进入了海军司令部服务器
I'm inside the Naval Command server.
写入指令
Draft the order.
什么指令？
What order?
我们就快弄完了
We're almost done here
你也没什么利用价值了
and I really don't have any use for you anymore.
不，不，不要！
No, No. No!
不！不要！
No! No!
不！不！不要！不要！
No! No! No! No!
不！
No!
埃里克，我要战术队驻守原地
Erik, I want your tac teams to hold their position.
不能冒险让他们被卫星拍到
We can't run the risk of them being seen on satellite.
他们将与你保持两英里距离
They'll be two miles behind you.
所有小队都会原地等你信号
All teams will be standing by for your signal.
慢着！
Hold on!
刚才怎么了？
What the hell was that?
鲍尔，凯特，说话
Bauer. Kate, come in.
出来，凯特
Come on, Kate.
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
他们肯定挂了
我作证
卡车里有两个枪手，准备好了么？
We got two shooters in the truck. You ready?
好了
Yeah.
走
Go.
快走！往前走！
Move on! Move up!
接收者：马萨诸塞号战列舰
发送者：美国战略司令部
是核潜艇
That's a nuclear sub.
是的
Yes, it is.
你调用它做什么？
What are you ordering it to do?
好了
Ready.
发吧
Send it.
信息已发送
长官，有战术行动指令
Sir, incoming tactical action message.
看看吧
Let's do it.
是什么，长官？
What is it, sir?
射击指令
Fire order.
击沉中国沈阳号航母
We're to sink the Chinese carrier Shenyang.
会是军事演习么？
Could this be a drill?
是确切指令
Confirmed.
从战略司令部下达的
Direct from Strategic Command.
我是船长
This is the captain.
装载一号和二号鱼雷管
Flood torpedo tubes one and two.
准备发射
Make ready for launch.
遵命
Aye, sir.
声纳，定位沈阳号
Sonar, give me a solution on the Shenyang.
一八五方向，距离七英里
Bearing one-eight-five, seven miles.
零三零航向，12节航速
Course zero-three-zero at 12 knots.
所有鱼雷管就位
All tubes report ready.
发射一号和二号鱼雷
Fire torpedoes one and two.
天啊
Oh, my God.
更多原创翻译字幕请访问
TLF论坛：http://bbs.eastgame.org
TLF中文字幕站：http://sub.eastgame.org
TLF字幕组微博：http://weibo.com/tlfsubs